[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I'm great.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "How are you doing, Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "I'm good.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 49, "question": "If you lose there, that's a big problem if you are presumed to be a frontrunner, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 50, "answer": "For sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "How do you answer that charge?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "Well, you know, it just makes me laugh out loud.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Rick Santorum"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 100, "question": "Why do you think that is and how will this play out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "CC", "WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 101, "answer": "Well, I certainly think it's driven by the presence of Rick Santorum.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 133, "question": "What do you make of the current GOP race?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 134, "answer": "I have to correct that I served on a panel that President Bush appointed but I didn't work in his White House.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Romney", "Rick Santorum"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "So how effective is it to go carpet-bomb your opponents like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "I think that Romney has rendered himself unelectable in the general election and I think Rick Santorum, if he had stayed with the blue-collar narrative would have been much better off than heading into the religious rights territory that turns off moderates.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 154, "question": "I mean is that even a possibility, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 155, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "RB", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNPS", "VBP", "VBN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "Well, it's a horrible fact of life that money decides elections and that now after what the Republicans have done negative money with no limits can really corrupt the process.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 289, "question": "Be honest?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 290, "answer": "Honestly, I explained that, you know, I feel like I am trying to create a dialogue and end this clash of civilization.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 297, "question": "So what did your -- what did your father say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 298, "answer": "He said, Allah be with you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 299, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 300, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "``", "NNP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "''", "VB", "RB", "VB", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 302, "question": "Your father said that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 303, "answer": "My father made \"Alexander the Great,\" don't forget, who was a great unifier of people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "When you met him, did you bring up this denial of the Holocaust that he keeps purporting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBG", "RP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "TONE: No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "Do you stand by that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bush"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 376, "question": "Don't they have a right to feel vulnerable about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 377, "answer": "So you basically are defending the preventive war doctrine, which goes back to Bush.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "You have a new television ad that labels him a fake, why?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Because he's a fake.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "Do you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "I don't think the party has a clue who is going to be the nominee, after watching last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 460, "question": "Is this a debate they should be having, given that the rest of America is screaming about jobs and the economy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 461, "answer": "I couldn't agree with you more that he's taken the exact wrong tack on this.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 466, "question": "Is there a danger that this particular obsessive debate with social conservative issues is just going to make them look rather out of touch with modern America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 467, "answer": "I don't think that it was the candidates so much that wanted to focus on these issues.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Carol Roth", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 473, "question": "You can even take that a step further, which is how many more mandates might there be buried in Obamacare?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 474, "answer": "Carol Roth, I mean, Mitt Romney is still I guess de facto the front-runner.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"], "TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "What is the problem for Mitt Romney, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "The problem with Mitt Romney is the same problem that all the candidates had last night.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 525, "question": "If he was to lose in Michigan, then that's bad for him, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 526, "answer": "It would be a disaster.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Michigan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 544, "question": "Super Tuesday is going to be the really big indicator as to whether Mitt Romney can become a proper front-runner, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "TO", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 545, "answer": "Well, I think it is because, of course, it's all of those states in contention that night.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Tuesday"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120223pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "That's not coming across in these debates?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "I totally agree.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]